module.exports = {
    "CZ 3002":[
        {question:"What is 1 + 1",answers:["1","2","30","50"],ans:1},
        {question:"What is 10 + 1",answers:["18","22","11","24"],ans:2},
    ],
    "CZ 2001":[
        {question:"What is 1 + 1",answers:["1","2","30","50"],ans:1},
        {question:"What is 10 + 1",answers:["18","22","11","24"],ans:2},
    ],
    "CZ 1001":[
        {question:"What is 1 + 1",answers:["1","2","30","50"],ans:1},
        {question:"What is 10 + 1",answers:["18","22","11","24"],ans:2},
    ],
    "CZ 1002":[
        {question:"What is 1 + 1",answers:["1","2","30","50"],ans:1},
        {question:"What is 10 + 1",answers:["18","22","11","24"],ans:2},
    ],
    "CZ 1003":[
        {question:"What is 1 + 1",answers:["1","2","30","50"],ans:1},
        {question:"What is 10 + 1",answers:["18","22","11","24"],ans:2},
    ],
};